A Guide to the Wallis family papers, 1806-1877
Library of Virginia
Library of Virginia
Wallis family papers, 1806-1877
The Library of Virginia
53441
.225 cubic feet (1 box)
Wallis family
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Acquisition Information
Purchased.
Biographical Information
The Wallis family was a prominent family in Culpeper County, Virginia. Captain George Wallis was the father of George Wallis, Jr., by his first wife, and the father of William S. Wallis by his second wife.
Scope and Content
Papers, 1806-1977, of the Wallis family of Culpeper County, Virginia, consisting of accounts, bonds, deeds, lists, promissory notes, receipts, and other papers. Accounts are with local merchants for the purchase of goods; bonds and promissory notes are for the borrowing of money; and receipts are for the purchase of items and for the payment of accounts and of taxes. Papers include a deed for 100 acres in Culpeper County and a list of mares for mating with a horse.
Contents List
- Papers, 1806-1812 (Folder 1)
- Papers, 1814-1817 (Folder 2)
- Papers, 1822-1825 (Folder 3)
- Papers, 1825-1829 (Folder 4)
- Papers, 1830-1832 (Folder 5)
- Papers, 1832-1833 (Folder 6)
- Papers, 1835-1838 (Folder 7)
- Papers, 1840-1841 (Folder 8)
- Papers, 1843-1847 (Folder 9)
- Papers, 1848-1849 (Folder 10)
- Papers, 1851-1855 (Folder 11)
- Papers, 1860-1861 (Folder 12)
- Papers, 1874-1877, undated (Folder 13)